(hissing)
(grunts)
(cackling)
(grunting)
Haaaa!
I've got you now!
Huh?
What's in that
blood he spits out?
Some kind of poison?
What's this?
You're too strong.
That's not very much fun at all.
(warbling)
Straw Doll Technique: Resonance!
(upbeat music)
(chittering)
Tsk! How many of them are there?
I guess we just keep going
like it's whack-a-mole, huh?
Yeah.
Keep going.
Keep on exorcising them.
We'll just wipe out all of them.
It's unlikely to retaliate.
I do get what you're saying...
Its technique
covers a large area,
so its main body doesn't
have much offense.
I just said it's unlikely.
All the things we
were worried about,
its technique's range, the
number of victims, the barrier.
All of those are subtracting
from its main body.
So we're lucky.
We'll be able to
exorcise it quickly, then.
Which means, the real
problem comes after.
(gasp)
Kugisaki!
I'll be fine.
You just whack the mole!
Damn it!
She keeps getting
sucked into things!
But what was that just now?
The mole?
That earlier one?
No, it's neither!
Kugisaki?
Oh, hey, it's my older brother!
Huh?
Me too, me too!
It took off!
Should I just let it go?
No, go after it!
Kugisaki and that thing
both went outside the barrier!
She might be going
up against something
even more dangerous
than we assumed!
By contrast, things
here aren't so bad,
I can handle this by myself!
Save Kugisaki!
Go!
Alright but if
things go bad here
then you follow us and get out!
Why, you!
Don't touch me!
I didn't realize
you were a woman.
But you are.
Sorry.
Yecchh.
We brothers were tasked
with a certain errand you see.
But killing jujutsu sorcerers
isn't part of that arrangement.
So if you withdraw
we'll let you escape.
Young woman.
An errand?
Hmm?
I presumed you were
on the same errand.
A cursed spirit
or a cursed user?
Which is he?
And what is that smell?
(monster warbling)
(grunting)
Last one!
You're not even trying.
This is too easy.
I told you you're
making this too easy!
(sigh)
And that's the last of them.
So Tsumiki is safe
for the moment.
Now, I just have to...
(dripping)
One survived?
So that wasn't its
main body after all?
The barrier hasn't
collapsed, either!
What the?
I shouldn't be trying
too hard to find logic
in a cursed spirit's
behavioral patterns.
But the fact is,
that question has been
nagging me this whole time.
Why did it just
now start killing the
humans it had marked?
The first one was
killed back in June.
And in June...
Our only objective here
is get Sukuna's finger and
return it to where it belongs.
(evil cackle)
(opening theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
Some have a presence
that's too overwhelming.
Some keep very quiet.
Some have already been
absorbed by a cursed spirit.
This is resonance.
Sukuna's finger kept
its power repressed
within the cursed spirit
that had absorbed it.
But back in June, when
Sukuna manifested in Itadori,
it released its cursed energy.
This one looks the same
as the one from the
juvenile detention center,
but it's probably
several degrees
(gasp)
(grunt)
stronger!
(chuckle)
Nue!
Aah.
Guess I win again.
This is unusual.
You rarely ask me
to train you, Megumi.
Are you trying to
catch back up to Yuji?
Well, I guess beggars
can't be choosers.
It really bothers you that much?
To ask me for help?
Listen, Megumi.
I think you have
just as much ability
and potential as Yuji does.
The only thing holding
you back is your mindset.
Megumi.
You don't know how to
bring out your best, do you?
Huh?
Are you saying I haven't
been giving it my best?
I'm not saying you
haven't, I'm saying you can't.
For example, in the ball game...
Why did you lay down
that sacrifice bunt?
(grunt)
Was it to advance the runner
even though it meant
that you'd be out?
That is good team play.
But Yuji would always go for
a home run, and so would I.
I'm not saying a bunt is bad.
Baseball is a team sport.
And everyone has
their role to play.
But jujutsu sorcery
is an individual sport.
Isn't working with the
other sorcerers important?
Of course.
But no matter how many
allies you have around you,
when you die you'll be alone.
You can only piece
together undervalued data
on yourself and others.
You can't imagine a stronger
future version of yourself.
Maybe that's because
of your trump card?
You believe that
in the worst case,
you can resolve everything
at the cost of your life.
But at that point,
forget about beating me.
You'll never even
measure up to Nanami.
Dying to win and
risking death to win,
are completely
different, Megumi.
Give it your best.
Be greedier.
How many seconds
was I unconscious?
My Demon Dog's destroyed.
No, the technique was released.
(evil cackle)
So I guess, this is it for me.
Sacred treasure!
Sacred swing!
Hmph.
Kind of a waste of your talents.
(light chuckle)
Oh what the hell?
A jujutsu sorcerer's
growth curve
isn't necessarily
a gentle slope.
One thing I don't get.
Why did you run, back then?
Spit out the entire
depths of my shadow.
Worry about a
specific structure later.
Just push it out as soon as
I collect the cursed energy.
Imagine a future
version of myself,
who's freely
surpassed my limits!
Oh I can do that!
[Gojo] With a strong foundation
and a little bit of
sense and imagination,
it just takes the slightest
trigger to change a person.
Domain Expansion:
Chimera Shadow Garden!
It's incomplete!
And it's ugly work at best!
But for now, that's fine!
Broaden it
more freely!
The interpretation
of the technique!
(lightning strikes)
(intense music)
(rising roar)
(giggle)
Demon Dog Totality's claws
were able to injure that thing.
So they'd have no trouble
piercing through you
when you're caught off-guard.
I'm tired.
Now, for the other guys.
Where'd they go?
Good!
That's very good!
(retching)
"Jujutsu Kaisen"
There's one fundamental
rule for interacting with others.
You know what that is?
[Bully] No I don't.
It's simple.
It's "I won't kill you,
"so in return please
don't kill me either."
Substitute any word for "kill".
The point is drawing a line
so you don't
infringe on the other.
In order for both
to exist together
they need to honor that.
Just strutting around
breaking that rule,
so that others have to
try not to piss you off
must have made
you feel powerful,
Next time you do it
around me, I'll kill you.
Yeah but, what did
we ever do to you?
Figure it out yourself or die.
[Takeda] Hey you!
T-T-T-T-Today I tell off
Ikezawa and his gang!
I'm not gonna be their
stupid gofer anymore!
Yeah you tell 'em
Do it!
Oh but Aida,
that's just gonna make
me their next target!
So do me a favor
and don't try too hard!
Oh not a chance fatty!
I'm done messing around!
Starting today,
I'm gonna tell 'em
you're my new replacement!
Dude, you'd sell
out your best friend?
You're damn right I would!
[Tsumiki] Megumi.
Hey, look!
Isn't that Ikezawa and his
buddies piled up over there?
You told me you
wouldn't fight anymore.
Yeah well you're not my mom.
I hate bad people.
They act so damn superior
when their empathy
and imagination
are as empty as a vacant lot.
I can't deal with
good people either.
Because they forgive
those bad people.
And they view the act of
forgiveness as a noble thing.
Makes me want to vomit.
Tsumiki's a perfect
example of a good person.
I detest you.
Agh! Sorry!
I didn't think it
would come out!
When I was in first grade
my father and Tsumiki's mother,
the two of them hooked up,
and vanished without a trace.
A suspicious
white-haired man told us...
The thing about your dad...
He's from a big clan
among the jujutsu sorcerers
called the Zen'in.
They're so inept
even I'm freaked out.
Your father left the
clan in order to have you.
Megumi.
Your father was saving
you as the ultimate card
to use against the Zen'in clan.
Pisses you off, huh?
That solved the mystery
of how they got enough
money to disappear.
Apparently, I had been
sold to that Zen'in clan.
And yeah, it pissed me off.
Especially his lack
of tact about it.
And that irritating guy stopped
my sale to the Zen'in clan.
And used the promise
that I would work
as a jujutsu
sorcerer as collateral
in order to get financial
aid from Jujutsu High
to support us both.
What's this jujutsu
sorcerer crap, anyway?
It's bullshit.
Who the hell would I ever save?
Hey, Tsumiki!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
Hi Megumi!
Oh nothing.
Hey, hold on.
Did you give any thought
to the test of courage
I was telling you about?
I don't want to do it,
but I'll go because
I'm worried about you.
Shortly after I started ninth
grade, Tsumiki was cursed.
The identity was unknown.
The origin was unknown.
But there were several victims
of the same curse nationwide.
All I found out was that
nobody knew anything.
And Tsumiki was left in a coma.
If I had the time
to curse someone,
I'd rather spend it
thinking about people I love.
She always smiled and
spouted noble ideals.
Not forgiving people
isn't such a bad thing.
It just goes along
with your kindness.
She even accepted
my strange disposition.
Yet Tsumiki would
get genuinely angry
whenever I hurt someone.
And that irritated me,
because I thought
it was hypocritical
in light of her
leave-others-be policy.
But now I realize I
had the wrong idea.
Just as I choose who I save,
she was choosing
me to worry about.
I'm sorry!
I was just a kid!
I apologize!
So wake up already
my stupid sister!
Damn my head hurts!
This Yasohachi Bridge curse
was just overlapping
the other one.
I doubt the curse that put
Tsumiki into a coma was undone.
Now I just have to tell Itadori
the news about
Sukuna's finger, but...
How?
"Fushiguro Fell Asleep"
(shock gasps)
A huge presence just
suddenly appeared.
Has Sukuna's finger
left the barrier?
If a sorcerer exorcised
the finger's host,
they're quite good.
But even if the
others have the finger,
and even if the special-grade
cursed spirit was defeated,
they wouldn't have
come out unscathed.
I hope they're okay.
Actually, on second thought,
please forget
everything I just said.
Hold it right there!
Damn, he's going
after the finger!
You think you can mock me?
Dancing around like
that and still getting away?
The thing is I'm a bit
insecure about my back
so it's only fair
that I warn you.
If you see my back,
I'll be forced to ki--
Oh!
Kugisaki!
Oh here you are, brother!
(screams)
-What the hell is that?
-Oh I'm sorry brother!
It wasn't on purpose! I
didn't mean to see that!
Now I have to kill you!
That must be the
source of that weird smell.
Why don't you just cover it up?
'Cause then it gets musty!
Rot Technique!
Supreme Art!
Wing King!
Death by Wasp!
(ending theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
[Unison] Juju Stroll!
Gojo!
Kugisaki!
(annoyed sigh)
So annoying.
It's way too hot out here
for your nonsense, Itadori.
Fushiguro is getting hit on!
Formation B!
[Unison] Roger that!
[Both] Fushiguro, no!
Who is this woman, Fushiguro?
Don't tell me you've
forgotten that night?
That special night
we had together
when you looked longingly at me
and made that toast to
the beauty of my eyes!
Whoa, what's with you?
Seriously, you two?
Could you please take
your hands off him?
You homewreckers!
Megumi has violin
practice with me now.
Let's get you back home,
Megumi, so you can warm up.
Today I think we'll
try something new,
and I'll have you master
"Twinkle Twinkle Little Star."
It's okay, don't mind them.
The station's straight ahead.
Just go that way.
Thank you so much.
[Unison] Huh?
Okay, seriously, what's up?
You three are totally
embarrassing me.
Stop doing that!
(embarrassed laugh)
(upbeat music)
"Episode 24: The Origin
of Blind Obedience"